smsgatewayhub.com 2016-11-26

# Bulk sms Policy, Bulk sms Privacy Policy, Bulk sms India

### Why it's safe

#### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the Services offered by the Company through the Site. Company may from time to time modify this Privacy Policy to reflect the current practices and policies employed by the Company for your data.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:

### SMSGATEWAYHUB Technologies Resourses Pvt Ltd.

**Add.:** 201, Royal Ratan Building (Opp. Kasliwal honda) 7, MG Road. Indore (M.P.) Pin : 452001  
**Tel:** +91.731.6450666  
**Mobile:** +919907922122  
**Email:** support@smsgatewayhub.com

#### Information we collect:

We may collect your Personally identifiable information, financial details (e.g., credit card no., login IDs/ user names for using third party payment services), technical details, content transmitted through the Service, etc. You are required to provide these details at the time of registering at the Site, or at the time of making any payments for purchasing the Company's Service, or at the time you access the Site.

#### How we use the collected information:

**We use your personally identifiable information and financial to:**

  * Identify you as a user of Company's Services;
  * Provide access to the Services;
  * Provide regular updates to you about new features and promotions associated with the Services;
  * Provide updates related to any other service offered by the Company and its affiliates;
  * Facilitate payment transactions you conclude through the Site at third party payment service providers;
  * Share it with third party service providers required for provision of Company's Services;
  * Improve security infrastructure, Company employs to protect your information.

**We use any technical information provided by you to:**

  * To store a small text based files, called Cookies, to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving the Service and tracking user trends.
  * When you access the Site, Company's servers automatically record information that your browser sends to the Server.

**We use your contents transmitted through the Service to:**

  * Provide access to the Service;
  * Comply with any regulatory directions and orders;

#### Third party Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to Company's services. Company has no control over any third party Sites or links that may be available at the Site. You are, therefore, advised to check the privacy policy applicable to such third party Sites before You share any of your information with them.  
If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

#### Security

Company employs appropriate security measures to protect any information that you may provide. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. However, Company does not claim that such security measures may be sufficient due to inherent nature and security risks associated with information transmitted through internet.

#### Disclosure

Apart for disclosing your information to a third party service provider, Company may share your information with security agencies in case it is required to comply with any court order or governmental direction. Company may also disclose your information to enforce the Terms or to prevent any breach of Terms.

#### Accessing your data

You may access, modify and remove your personal information by accessing your use account at the Site. Company may ask for your identity proof to verify your antecedents to prevent any unauthorized disclosure or misuse of data.
